Harrison Weisberg

Marina del Rey, CA 90292 | 845-641-0864 | hpweisberg@gmail.com github.com/hpweisberg | linkedin.com/in/harrisonweisberg

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Software Engineer who is hungry for the latest cutting-edge tech and the creative experience to make a front-end stand out. I have a variety of past experiences where I've helped fortune 500 companies like Marriott and Under Armour in brand management and PR. Before making the leap to coding I also had experience in technical sales for a SaaS company, giving me a different perspective on client needs and issues that arise from new user needs.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS

Back-End: Node.js, REST API, RESTful Routing, JSON API

Libraries: React, Express.js, Bootstrap

Databases: MongoDB, Mongoose, SQL, PostgreSQL, Sequelize

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

CAST - GitHub | App

Helping Casting Directors find their next star for any upcoming project (mobile first)

- Collaborated with a team to build a MERN stack app utilizing a DB access user-created data
- Created several components including actor cards and details to match renderings of our wireframes
- Conducted Github management of the project, led stand-ups & downs, and managed Trello Board

FLYv - GitHub | App

Share upcoming flights and journey updates with your friends and family

- Utilized RESTful routing while incorporating CRUD on models including embedded and referenced
- Built a friend system with unid to link user profiles to a friend array for access to upcoming flights and blogs
- Crafted a one-page experience by simulating the use of components for an easy UX

MAMBA - GitHub | App

Help Kobe Bryant collect NBA Championship Trophies in a game of Snake

- Rendered game state on the game grid to simulate snake movement
- Utilized classic CSS to design MAMBA from the ground up without frameworks
- Created a timeout loop based on the game speed to simulate walls

EXPERIENCE

Meltwater, Key Account Manager

Marina del Rey, CA, 04/2022 - 11/2022

- Managed 50+ client relationships for a mid-size Sass company, including Lime, Docker, and Turo
- Partnered with clients to improve campaign performance and troubleshoot any challenges with the software

Nielsen, Sports Account Manager

New York, NY, 03/2021 - 03/2022

- Conducted data analysis in Excel for clients including Nike, Comcast, P&G, Oakley
- Led the creation of client reports and presentations by providing insight and advising on strategy

William Morris Endeavor (Formerly 160over90), PR Account Coordinator

New York, NY, 03/2019 - 10/2020

- Conducted marking efforts that garnered local and national media exposure
- Successfully ran in-person and social activations for brands that exceeded coverage by 20% or greater

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Remote, Certificate Expected: 03/2023

Full-stack software engineering 420+ hour program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies

Quinnipiac University

Hamden, CT, Graduated: 06/2016

Bachelor's Degree in Film, Television, and Interactive Media